<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LOOK dataset</title><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on LOOK dataset</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Releasing the LOOK Dataset</title><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/Release/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/Release/</guid><description>The LOOK dataset is finally online! Please look at the intructions below in order to understand how the dataset has been created.
Introduction We provide an open-source, high quality labeled dataset for the in-the-wild eye contact detection task. Eye contact detection is a practically important task to better understand and forecast human behaviors. In particular,autonomous robots and self driving cars need to solve this task to navigate safely around humans, and act accordingly to this new modality.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/authors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/authors/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/contribute/</guid><description>Contribute to the project You have a query? You think that the task is exciting and you want to contribute to the project? Please contact the authors.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/dataset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/dataset/</guid><description>Download the dataset Automatic download Download simply everything from here.
You want to download everything from raw data? Follow the steps here for each dataset:
Manual download Nuscenes Nuscenes mainly consists of high resolution images with some crowded scenes on a traffic configuration.
Training set Go to Nuscenes official website and download the sweeps from CAM_BACK_LEFT in US. Go to Nuscenes official website and download the samples from CAM_FRONT in US.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/github/</guid><description>Visualization code Copy the following python file or download it from here:
import argparse import os import errno from PIL import Image import numpy as np import cv2 parser = argparse.ArgumentParser(description=&amp;#39;Script to build the LOOK dataset visualization&amp;#39;) parser.add_argument(&amp;#39;--path_gt&amp;#39;, dest=&amp;#39;pgt&amp;#39;, type=str, help=&amp;#39;path to the annotation file&amp;#39;, default=&amp;#34;./annotations.csv&amp;#34;) parser.add_argument(&amp;#39;--path_images&amp;#39;, dest=&amp;#39;pot&amp;#39;, type=str, help=&amp;#39;path to the LOOK dataset&amp;#39;, default=&amp;#34;&amp;#34;) parser.add_argument(&amp;#39;--path_output_images&amp;#39;, dest=&amp;#39;poi&amp;#39;, type=str, help=&amp;#39;path to the output images&amp;#39;, default=&amp;#34;&amp;#34;) def makedirectory(path): try: os.makedirs(path) except OSError as e: if e.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/licenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://looking-vita-epfl.github.io/top/licenses/</guid><description>According to the official websites of JRDB, Nuscenes and Kitti:
JRDB Dataset is under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Licence. Kitti Dataset is under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 Licence. Nuscenes Dataset is under Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 4.0 International Public Licence.</description></item></channel></rss>